let quiz=[
    {
        question:"Which of these methods of class StringBuffer is used to extract a substring from a String object?",
        option:[
            "1.substring()",
            "2.Substring()",
            "3.SubString()",
            "4.None of the mentioned",
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these can be overloaded?",
        option:[
            "1.Methods",
            "2.Constructors",
            "3.All of the mentioned",
            "4.None of the mentioned",
            
        ],
        answer:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these process occur automatically by java run time system?",
        option:[
            "1.Serialization",
            "2.Memory allocation",
            "3.Deserialization",
            "4.All of the mentioned",   
        ],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these interface handle sequences?",
        option:[
            "1.Set",
            "2.List",
            "3.Comparator",
            "4.Collection",   
        ],
        answer:2,

    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following classes can catch all exceptions which cannot be caught?",
        option:[
            "1.RuntimeException",
            "2.Error",
            "3.Exception",
            "4.ParentException",   
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"What decides thread priority?",
        option:[
            "1.Process",
            "2.Process scheduler",
            "3.Thread",
            "4.Thread scheduler",
            
        ],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these packages contains all the classes and methods required for event handling in Java?",
        option:[
            "1.java.applet",
            "2.java.awt",
            "3.java.event",
            "4.java.awt.event",
            
        ],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question:"Which file separator should be used by MANIFEST file?",
        option:[
            "1. /",
            "2. \\",
            "3. -",
            "4. //",
            
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the below is not a session tracking method?",
        option:[
            "1.URL rewriting",
            "2.History",
            "3.Cookies",
            "4.SSL sessions",
            
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which file is used to define dependency in maven?",
        option:[
            "1.build.xml",
            "2.pom.xml",
            "3.dependency.xml",
            "4.version.xml",
            
        ],
        answer:2,
    }
]
